[{"answer": "You've just got to get away.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "What goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, there's no single answer.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "And what is the answer?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "It's -- it's perspective, but it's also understanding that there are seasons.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "So I think perspective probably has to be brought into this, right?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Oh, I love the man I voted for originally.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Do you like what you see for, maybe, the second term Obama already?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Well, it -- it is.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "America needs to find other business models, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I've seen it happen with people that have lost their children.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Does it apply to any form of trauma or are there grades of trauma?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "We just had -- we just had a shooting at our school.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "What is your emergency?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Chardon High School.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Ma'am, what school?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Chardon High School?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "Where's the shooter with the gun?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "What I -- what I really -- what was going through my mind was I had to get out of the high school and really nothing else flows through your mind.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "The moment you were shot, what goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "I had a lot of support.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "How did you deal with it?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "I mean, I did, yes.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Did -- did you despair?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Well, I had a lot of support from other people texting me and calling me that are in wheelchairs.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Or what was it that they did that helped you?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "It really doesn't happen really.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "What was that like for you as his mother?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "They said that they were cautiously optimistic when they came out of surgery, but -- so, we're still hoping and praying.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "What is the prognosis they made?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, if somebody who has been through it but has an outlook that's positive.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "-- is that a very particular support group that knows exactly what you've been through?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "I would love that.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Shake on it?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Does that bring all back?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, I had to -- I had to switch around my career a little bit that that I was aiming for.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "But aside from that, have you set yourself things that you really want to achieve?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I wanted to be just an electrician in the union and I don't believe that can happen practically right now.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "What would you want to be?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "I was doing a lot of current therapies, you know, psychiatry, psychology, which I started in 2011.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Before you met Tony, what was -- what was your life like?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Did it help, any of that?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Basically, insomnia.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "So, you had -- why don't you tell him what your symptoms were at the time?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "The rock bottom moment for me in a sense was -- it was after my second divorce, just being --I pushed so many people away, couldn't figure out why I felt this way.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "What was the rock bottom moment for you?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting, and we've done this with hundreds of wounded warriors and different soldiers -- inside every human being we have trauma, his is extreme trauma, and there's a personality in him that was beyond wounded.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "What do you say in this situation?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Well, basically, he has to take back his life.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "What advice would you give him?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Methamphetamine, right.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "He built a small business to start with and one of those young women that worked for him was addicted to meth, is that right?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Why don't you share with him the story of how you end up in your new business?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "Things were going great.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Why wouldn't you listen to Tony Robbins?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "What was that like for you?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I think ferocity of spirit is critical for everybody, but we all have it.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Or do you have a little bit of (INAUDIBLE), which is that ferocity of spirit?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "You know, we do.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Do we all have it?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Most of it -- I think what's really beautiful about most human beings is that we'll do more for others we love than we'll ever do for ourselves.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Is that a good focus to look at children, to look at other things and say, \"You know, what stopped feeling sorry for myself; it's for him, for her, it's for that\"?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I got to tell you, Tony is absolutely right.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Mike, What do you say to these people suffering in America right now?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "But actually all those emotions are just barriers to getting back on your feet, aren't they?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "I -- certainly, I think without health, you're not around to do anything.", "docId": "130125pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "If I ask you if you can have anyone thing: you can have good health, you can have money, you can have the fame that allows you to inspire people, what would you choose as the one thing?", "qSentId": 694}]